A Guide to the Rodman C. Rockefeller papers FA1350
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Business Interests, 1960-2001; I; 10.53 Cubic Feet 24 letter document boxes and 3 legal document boxes
  - Booker McConnell PLC, Reports and Accounts, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Booker McConnell PLC, Reports and Accounts, 1988-1989 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Booker Agriculture International, 1982-1983, Annual Reports (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Booker Agriculture International, 1990-1991, Annual Reports (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Booker Agriculture International, 1993-1994, Annual Reports (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Booker McConnell PLC, Supplementary Material (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Grupo ICA, 1982-1983, Annual Report (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation, Annual Report, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Doane Farm Management Company, Supplementary Material (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Professional Appointment Books, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Professional Appointment Books, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Professional Appointment Books, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Professional Appointment Books, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Professional Appointment Books, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Professional Appointment Books, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Professional Appointment Books, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Professional Appointment Books, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Professional Appointment Books, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Professional Appointment Books, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Professional Appointment Books, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Professional Appointment Books, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Professional Appointment Books, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Professional Appointment Books, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Professional Appointment Books, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Changing Patterns in Business Responsibility, Cleveland, Ohio, 1967 March 30 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - The Impact of US Technology on Overseas Development, Harvard Club, New York City, 1966 October 24 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - The Church and Economic Life - Corporate Power and Responsibility - National Council of Churches, New York, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Remarks at Dedication, Housing Ceremony, Lima, Peru, 1966 February 15 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Profits for Progress - National Conference on Equal Business, Washington D.C., 1965 September 25 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - What is Economic Freedom, 100 Men, Inc. New York, 1965 September 15 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - The New Nature of Corporations, Dartmouth Talk - Business Week, 1965 July 17 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - "What Builders Look For in Joint Ventures (in Latin America)", Inter -American Building Conference, San Juan, Puerto Rico, 1970 July 22 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Rodman C. Rockefeller's Statement to Open Press Conference (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Investment Opportunities in the Americas Inter-American Cattlemen's Assoc., San Antonio, Texas, 1969 December 5 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Ward Howell Association Luncheon, 1969 October 16 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Urban Economic Development, Chicago Economic Development Dinner, Chicago, Illinois, 1969 September 26 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - A New Definition of Management - The American Management Association - New York City, 1969 June 3 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - The Role of American Business in Aiding Underdeveloped Areas at Home and Abroad, 1968 November 6 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - Salutation Speech, 20th Anniversary, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Announcement of Capital Campaign - "Jefferson Moment". (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Interracial Council for Business Opportunity (ICBO) Los Angeles, 1965 June 10 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Economic Freedom - 1965, Shaw University, Raleigh, NC, 1965 March 26 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Double Ten Celebration, San Juan, Puerto Rico, Speech, 1964 November 23 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Report on Peru, U.S. Inter -American Council, Chicago, 1964 September 25 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - "Economic Development and Social Research", The Behavioral Scientist, 1964 September (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Economic Freedom - 1964 Elks Convention, August 25, 1964, Miami Beach (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Mamaroneck Community Leaders Dinner, 1964 September 10 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Private Participation in Rural Development - Interamerican Rural Youth Conference, Statler Hilton Hotel, New York, 1964 September 3 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Social Structure and Economic Development in Latin America, Princeton University, 1964 April 10 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Housing Division Review, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Study of International Housing - Submitted by Rodman C. Rockefeller, New York, 1963 February 21 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - The Role of Business in the Planning of International Development, New York, NY, 1963 November 7 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Statement on Housing (HR -8143), House Banking and Currency Committee, New York, 1963 August 23 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Creation of International Bank Board Would Drop Hope - Bomb in Latin American, New York, 1962 November 26 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Possible Break in the Latin American Housing Crisis - Hotel Pierre, NY, 1962 October 1 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Subcommittee on Inter-American Relationships, Washington, D.C., 1962 May 11 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - From an Idea to an International Business - Lawyers Title News, 1960 March (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - The International Council for Business Opportunity - Annual Reports, 1964-1985 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - The International Council for Business Opportunity - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Sementes Agroceres 25th Anniversary, Sao Paulo, Brazil, 1970 September 18 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Rhetoric and Reality - International Basic Economy Corporation, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Meeting the Challenges of Communication - Toronto, Canada, (IBEC), 1969 June 2 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - International Institute of Education, 80th Anniversary Gala (Remarks) Plaza Hotel, New York, 1999 October 14 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - International Institute of Education Regional Awards Dinner (Remarks), San Francisco, California, 1999 September 15 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Arbor Acres Farm Retirement Dinner, Glastonbury, CT, 1998 April 4 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Interesting Investment Opportunities for German Private Clients, Metzler Bank, Frankfurt, 1997 September 16 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - The Potential for Fulbright Exchange, 1997 June 16 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Aguila Aztec Award and Speech, 1996 March 11 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Is Clinton Headed into Trouble in Mexico, Op -Ed Draft, 1997 March 21 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Property Market Investment Opportunity Zurich, Switzerland, 1997 January 27 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Mexico - U.S. Business Committee 50th Plenary Meeting, Houston, Texas - Speech, 1996 June 10 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - "Fifty Years of Business Diplomacy" by Rodman C. Rockefeller, 1996 June (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Remarks on Brazilliam Trip, 1995 September 27 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - The Future of Mexus, 1994 June (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - XLIV Plenary Meeting - Mexico - U.S. Business Community - Orlando, FL, 1989 November 9 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Mexico - Beyond Debt Renegotiation, New York City, 1989 October 10 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Chamber of Commerce - Princeton Area - Scanticon, Princeton, 1989 June 1 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Mexico - "Third World Debtor or New World Economic Partner", University Club, NY, 1988 November 22 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Critical Movement for U.S. - Mexican Relations, 1988 October (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Mexico - U.S. Free Trade - Economy vs. Ecology, 1991 May 8 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Think Piece on Free Trade Agreement, 1991 February 26 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Lecture on NAFTA - Woodrow Wilson School, Princeton, NJ, 1990 October 9 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Roundtable of the National Association of International Business Economists, Washington D.C., 1990 September 25 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Canadian-American-Mexican Free Trade, Princeton Chamber of Commerce, Princeton, New Jersey, 1990 June 7 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Interracial Council for Business Opportunity (ICBO) 25th Anniversary, Hilton Hotel, NY, 1988 April 27 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Breakfast with President de la Madrid, Mexico-U.S. Business Committee, Los Pinos, 1988 February 15 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Mexico - U.S.- BC 42nd Plenary Meeting, New Orleans, LA, 1987 November 4 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - American Chamber of Commerce of Mexico - 70th Anniversary, New York, 1987 July 21 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - New York College of Osteopathic Medicine, Graduation Address, New York, 1987 June 10 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Mexico - U.S. Business Committee, Los Pinos, Mexico, 1987 February 16 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Remarks to President de la Madrid, Los Pinos, Mexico, 1985 February 11 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Impressions of Berlin, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Interracial Council for Business Opportunity (ICBO) Hilton, Hotel, 1983 April 27 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Tuck Associates Conference International - Portfolio Diversification (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - BAI and IBEC Board of Directors Dinner - Norfolk Hotel, Kenya, 1982 September 29 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Association of American Chamber of Commerce in Latin America, New York, 1981 April 22 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Outline of Doing Business with Mexico - Georgia, 1980 November 12 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Draft of Reciprocity of Need - Mutuality of Interests - Mexico Workshop, Boston, Massachusetts, 1980 March 19 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Building a Genetics Company: Nicolas - Turkey Conference, Santa Rosa, California, 1979 October 6 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Mexico and U.S. - Op -ed piece, New York Times, 1979 September 28 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Shortages We Share: New Challenges U.S. - Mexico Chamber of Commerce - Acapulco, Mexico, 1979 June 22 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Remarks at Meeting with President Perez and President Elect Herrera - Caracas, 1979 February 20 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Let's Export More American Technology, Memphis Economics Club - Memphis, TN, 1978 December 13 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Remarks at World Poultry Congress - Second Draft, 1978 September 26 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - World Food Situation - Food Industries Buyer's Guide, Hilton Hotel, New York, 1978 June 16 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Prospects for Brazilian Agriculture, Brazilian - American Chamber of Commerce, 1978 April 11 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Confronting Changed World Realities - National Fluid Power Association, Marcos Island, FL, 1976 February 24 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Agribusiness Councils, 3rd Investment - Mission to Brazil, 1976 January 26 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Sementes Agroceres, 30th Anniversary (IBEC) - Sao Paulo, Brazil, 1975 September 29 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - The Position of the U.S. and Today's Economic and Political Realities Council of the Americas - Washington, D.C., 1975 June 4 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Clark Equipment Corporation - Huron, Ohio, 1974 September 17 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - A New Basis for Hemispheric Cooperation, Commerce Club - Mexico City, 1974 January 30 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - A Proposal for Western Hemisphere Energy Policy, 1973 December (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Business and Social Progress (Speech Not Delivered), Mexico City, 1973 February (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Putting Corporate Directors to Work, 1972 December (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Speech: Coral Gables Chamber of Commerce - Coral Gables, FL, 1972 November 29 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) - 25th Anniversary, Tarrytown, NY, 1972 October (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Towards a New Business Responsibility - Venezuelan Executives Association, Caracas, Venezuela, 1972 September 21 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - The Role of Business - Doing Well or Doing Good, Address by Rodman C. Rockefeller, Hotel St. Regis, New York, 1972 April 13 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) - 25th Anniversary Reception - Sao Paulo, Brazil, 1972 January 28 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Oportunidades en el Campo de Agricultura en las Americas, 1971 December 4 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - National Foreign Trade Council - The Americas Luncheon, New York City, Cali, Colombia, 1971 November 15 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Myths and Realities Facing Managers in the Hemisphere - Cali, Colombia (Speech), 1971 September 8-10 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Private Investment and Latin American Council on Foreign Relations Session, New York, 1971 May 12 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Turn Public Problems to Private Accoutn - J. Walter Thompson Company Luncheon, New York, 1971 March 17 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - What is a Donation Worth - United Appeal Luncheon, Cleveland, Ohio, 1970 October 15 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - The New York Society of Security Analysts - New York City, 1970 September 25 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Mexico - Council of the Americas and Affiliate Correspondence, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Mexico - Mexus - NAFTA Articles (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Mexico - Mexus, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Mexico - Council of the Americas and Affiliates, 1998-1999 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Mexico - Council of the Americas and Affiliates Board Meeting, 1998 December 8 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Mexico - Council of the Americas and Affil. Joint Board of Directors and Adv. Committee Meeting, 1998 May 10 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Mexico - Mexus, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Mexico - Council of the Americas and Affiliates Board Meeting, 1997 December 9 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Mexico - Council of the Americas and Affiliates Board Meeting, 1997 September 18 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Mexico - Council of the Americas and Affiliates, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Mexico - Mexus, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Mexico - Council of the Americas and Affiliates - Strategic Planning Commission, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Mexico - Council of the Americas and Affiliates Board Meeting, 1996 December 18 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Mexico - Council of the Americas and Affiliates Board Meeting, 1996 December 11 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Mexico - Mexus, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Mexico - Council of the Americas and Affiliates, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Mexico - Mexus, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Mexico - Mexus - Rodman C. Rockefeller Resignation, 1994 August (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Mexico - Mexus, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Mexico - Mexus, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Mexico - Mexus NAFTA-Canada, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Mexico - Mexus, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Mexico - Mexus - Ecology vs. Economy, View of NAFTA Negotiations, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Mexico - Mexus, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Mexico - Council of the Americas and Affil. Chairman's Advisory Council, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Mexico - Mexus, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Mexico - Mexico Capital Growth Fund, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Mexico - Mexus, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Mexico - Mexus, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Mexico - Mexus, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Mexico - Mexus, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Mexico - Mexus, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Mexico - Mexus, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Mexico - Mexus, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Brazil - U.S. Business Council, 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Awards - Mex. Chamber of Commerce and Inst. Of Mexican Fin. Execs. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Council of the Americas and Affiliate Correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Commission on U.S. - Brazilian Business Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 24, Folder 9-10)
  - Council of the Americas and Affiliates Miscellaneous Pamphlets (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - International Basic Economy Corporation - Sale of CADA-Judibana, 1969-1976 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Trips (Primarily IBEC) (Box 68, Folder 2-28)
  - Trips (Primarily IBEC) (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Trips (Primarily IBEC) (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - IBEC Miscellaneous Photographs, 1985 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Image and Imagination - American Business, Harvard Business Review, 1966 July (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Interracial Council for Business Opportunity, Speech by Rodman C. Rockefeller, Vice President of IBEC, New York, 1966 April 21 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Social and Moral Responsibility in Businee, Arbor Acres Review, 1965 July (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Goals and Objectives for IBEC (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - Bohemian Grove Summer Encampment, Nicholas Turkey Breeding Farm, Pocantico Association, Inc., 1994 July 22-26 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Pan American Management Conference, Cali, Colombia, 1971 September (Box 83, Folder 9)
- Cultural Interests, 1969-2001; II; 5.59 Cubic Feet 11 letter document boxes and 3 legal document boxes
  - International Council of the Museum of Modern Art - Meetings and Itinerary, 1989 April-1990 July (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - International Council of the Museum of Modern Art - Spring Meeting in Milan, Italy, 1990 May 10-24 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Royal Windsor Horse-Carriage Show - Booker Board Meeting, International Council of the Museum of Modern Art - Spring Meeting in Milan, Italy, 1990 May (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - International Council of the Museum of Modern Art - Spring Meeting - Glasgow, Scotland, 1988 May 14-30 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - International Council of the Museum of Modern Art - Spring Meeting 1987 - Los Angeles, California, 1987 April 22-May 3 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - International Council of the Museum of Modern Art - Fall Meeting, 1986 - Madrid, Spain (Box 25, Folder 6)
    Restricted - Financial material
  - International Council of the Museum of Modern Art - Spring Meeting 1985 - Tokyo, Japan, 1985 April 13-29 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - International Council of the Museum of Modern Art - Fall Meeting 1984 - Boston, Massachusetts, 1984 October 14-19 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - International Council of the Museum of Modern Art - Spring Meeting 1984 - New York, New York, 1984 May 5-8 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - International Council of the Museum of Modern Art - Fall Meeting 1983 - New York, New York, 1983 November 6-9 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - International Council of the Museum of Modern Art - Fall Meeting 1982 - New York, New York, 1982 October 31-November 3 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Historic Hudson Valley Dinner, 1989 November 13 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - International Council of the Museum of Modern Art - Spring Meeting - San Antonio, Texas, 1989 April 14-23 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - International Council of the Museum of Modern Art - Spring Meeting 1988 - London, England, Frankfurt, Germany (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - International Council of the Museum of Modern Art - Spring Meeting 1987 - Los Angeles, California, 1987 April 22-May 3 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Folk Art Gallery - San Antonio, Texas, 1986 November 1-2 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - International Council of the Museum of Modern Art - Spring Meeting 1986 - Barcelona, Spain, 1986 April 12-21 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Sleepy Hollow Restoration Benefits, 1985-1986 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - International Council of the Museum of Modern Art - Spring Meeting 1985 - Tokyo, Japan, 1985 April 12-29 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - International Council of the Museum of Modern Art - Spring Meeting 1985 - Tokyo, Japan, 1985 April 12-29 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Trip to Colonial Williamsburg, Virginia, 1980 April 25-27 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - American Museum of Natural History - Lima, Peru, The Amazon, Macho Pichu, 2001 February 24-March 9 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - American Museum of Natural History - Lima, Peru, The Amazon, Macho Pichu (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Monticello Dinner, 2001 April 13-14 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - U.S. -Mexico Commission for Education and Cultural Exchange Dinner, 1998 November 12 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Center for Latin American Art - San Antonio Museum of Art, 1998 October 23 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Monticello Dinner at the Knickerbockers Club, 1998 May 7 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - International Council of the Museum of Modern Art - Meeting in Bombay, India, 1998 January 11-February 1 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Council of Mexico - U.S. Business Committee, Mexico, 1997 October 29-30 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Trip to Philadelphia and Unionville (Museum Trip), 1996 November 14-15 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Monticello Cabinet Retreat and U.S. - Mexican Business Committee Plenary Meeting - Houston, Texas, 1996 June 7-11 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - International Rescue Committee - 1998 Freedom Awards Dinner, 1998 November 10 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Colonial Williamsburg, Virginia, 1995 April 21-24 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Monticello Fall Board Meeting, 1994 November 3-5 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation - Monticello Fall Meeting, 1994 October 7-8 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - U.S. - Mexican Commission Dinner - U.S. - Mexican Commission for Education and Cultural Exchange, 1994 May 24 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - U.S. - Mexican Commission Dinner - U.S. - Mexican Commission for Education and Cultural Exchange, 1994 May 24 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - White House Dinner in Honor of Thomas Jefferson - Spring Board Meeting, 1994 April 11-13 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Monticello Dinner at the River Club, 1993 October 6 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - The Nelson A. Rockefeller Center for the Social Sciences - 10th Anniversary and Art Exhibit at the Hood Museum, 1993 July 8-9 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - U.S. - Mexican Commission for Educational and Cultural Exchange Dinner at MOMA, 1993 May 27 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - U.S. - Mexican Commission for Educational and Cultural Exchange Dinner at MOMA, 1993 May 27 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation - Monticello, New Bern, North Carolina, 1991 April 12-14 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - National Audobon Society, 1991 March 13-16 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation, Monticello - Board Meeting - Charlottesville, Virginia, 1992 April 11-13 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Abby Aldrich Rockefeller Folk Art Center - Williamsburg, Virginia, 1992 April 25 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - International Council of the Museum of Modern Art - Spring Meeting, Bordeaux, France, 1993 April 17-25 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - The 250th Anniversary of Thomas Jefferson's Birth - Events at Monticello, 1993 May-September (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Visit to the Barnes Foundation and Winterthur and Brandywine Museum, 1991 September 13-15 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Trip to Northeast Harbor, Maine Trip on the "Night Train", 1991 August 15-31 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Historic Hudson Valley 40th Anniversary - Pocantico Hills, New York, 1991 June 22 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Historic Hudson Valley 40th Anniversary - Pocantico Hills, New York, 1991 June 22 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Museum Licensing Development - Geoffrey Samuels, 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - The Museum of Modern Art - Correspondence, 1990-1998 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - The Museum of Modern Art - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1989-1991 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - The Museum of Modern Art - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1992 April 8 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - The Museum of Modern Art - Board of Trustees Minutes, 1989-1993 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - The Museum of Modern Art - Prints and Illustrated Books, Board Meeting Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - The Museum of Modern Art - Prints and Illustrated Books, Board - Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - The Museum of Modern Art - Amended By-Laws, 1985 June 12 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Folk Art Collection, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - The International Council of the Museum of Modern Art - Spring and Fall Meeting Agendas, 1991-1999 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - The International Council of the Museum of Modern Art - Correspondence for Investment Committee and Fund Raising, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - The International Council for the Museum of Modern Art - Member List and Information (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - The Museum of Modern Art - Contributions and Membership Fees, 1980-1999 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - San Antonio Museum of Art - Correspondence, 1987-1996 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - The Whitney Museum - Correspondence, 1982-1987 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - The Whitney Museum - Correspondence, 1982-1987 (Box 28, Folder 3)